[
    {
        "question": "Profieldiepte",
        "options": [
            "Warning triangle",
            "Driving in reverse",
            "Tread depth or thickness",
            "Weather conditions"
        ],
        "answer": "Tread depth or thickness"
    },
    {
        "question": "Banden",
        "options": [
            "Military convoy",
            "Tires",
            "Sober",
            "Back seat"
        ],
        "answer": "Tires"
    },
    {
        "question": "Aquaplaning",
        "options": [
            "Following distance",
            "Aquaplaning",
            "Minimum speed",
            "Grass"
        ],
        "answer": "Aquaplaning"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ongevallen",
        "options": [
            "Right of way",
            "Skater",
            "Accidents",
            "By mistake"
        ],
        "answer": "Accidents"
    },
    {
        "question": "Reactietijd",
        "options": [
            "Both sides",
            "One-way road",
            "Merging onto the road",
            "Reaction time"
        ],
        "answer": "Reaction time"
    },
    {
        "question": "Invloed",
        "options": [
            "Affects",
            "Construction tractors",
            "Location",
            "Roadway (includes multiple lanes)"
        ],
        "answer": "Affects"
    },
    {
        "question": "Reageren",
        "options": [
            "Disabled vehicle",
            "Right rear light",
            "Responds",
            "Shark teeth"
        ],
        "answer": "Responds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Verlenen",
        "options": [
            "Grant",
            "Front seat",
            "Loading goods",
            "Solid line"
        ],
        "answer": "Grant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Uitsteken",
        "options": [
            "Protrudes",
            "Sign",
            "Loading goods",
            "Nothing"
        ],
        "answer": "Protrudes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Toerental",
        "options": [
            "Losing control",
            "Revolutions per minute (on the meter)",
            "Luggage box",
            "Headrest"
        ],
        "answer": "Revolutions per minute (on the meter)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Openbaar vervoer",
        "options": [
            "Public transport",
            "Freight vehicles",
            "Entry lane",
            "Flashing car light"
        ],
        "answer": "Public transport"
    },
    {
        "question": "Autop ech",
        "options": [
            "Fine",
            "Car breakdown",
            "Protrudes",
            "Reflector"
        ],
        "answer": "Car breakdown"
    },
    {
        "question": "Slachtoffer",
        "options": [
            "Urban area",
            "Board",
            "Injured",
            "Passenger"
        ],
        "answer": "Injured"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bewusteloos",
        "options": [
            "Handbrake",
            "Unconscious",
            "Sign",
            "Traffic jam"
        ],
        "answer": "Unconscious"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tekenn",
        "options": [
            "By mistake",
            "Sign",
            "Warning lights",
            "Specific speed"
        ],
        "answer": "Sign"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tegenliggers",
        "options": [
            "Honking",
            "Exiting the road",
            "Oncoming traffic",
            "Flashing yellow light"
        ],
        "answer": "Oncoming traffic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Keren",
        "options": [
            "Luggage box",
            "Turning around",
            "Protrudes",
            "Oncoming traffic"
        ],
        "answer": "Turning around"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bebouwde kom",
        "options": [
            "Urban area",
            "License plate",
            "Minimum speed",
            "Unconscious"
        ],
        "answer": "Urban area"
    },
    {
        "question": "Erf",
        "options": [
            "Curve",
            "Temporary stop",
            "Residential area",
            "Unconscious"
        ],
        "answer": "Residential area"
    },
    {
        "question": "Inhalen",
        "options": [
            "Residential area",
            "Responds",
            "Overtaking",
            "Branched"
        ],
        "answer": "Overtaking"
    },
    {
        "question": "Voertuig",
        "options": [
            "Trailer",
            "Fine",
            "Maximum speed",
            "Vehicle"
        ],
        "answer": "Vehicle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Motorvoertuigen",
        "options": [
            "Priority",
            "Exiting the road",
            "The road is wet",
            "Motor vehicles"
        ],
        "answer": "Motor vehicles"
    },
    {
        "question": "Voorrang",
        "options": [
            "The road is wet",
            "Flashing car light",
            "Unconscious",
            "Priority"
        ],
        "answer": "Priority"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stilstaan",
        "options": [
            "Right driving lane",
            "Distance",
            "Temporary stop",
            "Police and ambulance lights"
        ],
        "answer": "Temporary stop"
    },
    {
        "question": "Parkeren",
        "options": [
            "Luggage box",
            "Parking",
            "Reaction time",
            "Tread depth or thickness"
        ],
        "answer": "Parking"
    },
    {
        "question": "Overweg / Rail",
        "options": [
            "Pedestrians",
            "Fine",
            "Railway crossing",
            "Right of way"
        ],
        "answer": "Railway crossing"
    },
    {
        "question": "Eenrichtingsweg",
        "options": [
            "Car horn",
            "Vehicle",
            "One-way road",
            "Passenger"
        ],
        "answer": "One-way road"
    },
    {
        "question": "Adviessnelheid",
        "options": [
            "Grant",
            "Recommended speed",
            "Exiting the road",
            "Minimum speed"
        ],
        "answer": "Recommended speed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Maximumsnelheid",
        "options": [
            "Maximum speed",
            "Driving lane",
            "Driving in reverse",
            "Unconscious"
        ],
        "answer": "Maximum speed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Minimumsnelheid",
        "options": [
            "Minimum speed",
            "Aquaplaning",
            "Road surface",
            "Side street"
        ],
        "answer": "Minimum speed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bestuurders",
        "options": [
            "Turning around",
            "By mistake",
            "Drivers",
            "Allowed"
        ],
        "answer": "Drivers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Voetgangers",
        "options": [
            "Pedestrians",
            "Car breakdown",
            "Left rear light",
            "Passenger"
        ],
        "answer": "Pedestrians"
    },
    {
        "question": "Houd rekening met",
        "options": [
            "Pay attention to",
            "Affects",
            "Honking",
            "Luggage box"
        ],
        "answer": "Pay attention to"
    },
    {
        "question": "De pijl",
        "options": [
            "Reduce speed",
            "Warning triangle",
            "Arrow",
            "Specific speed"
        ],
        "answer": "Arrow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Aanhangwagen",
        "options": [
            "Prohibition",
            "Residential area",
            "Accurately",
            "Trailer"
        ],
        "answer": "Trailer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Verkeersbord",
        "options": [
            "Skater",
            "Tires",
            "Traffic sign",
            "Fuel"
        ],
        "answer": "Traffic sign"
    },
    {
        "question": "Het verbod",
        "options": [
            "Front fog light",
            "Prohibition",
            "City light",
            "License plate"
        ],
        "answer": "Prohibition"
    },
    {
        "question": "Verboden",
        "options": [
            "Weather conditions",
            "Police and ambulance lights",
            "Forbidden",
            "Rider"
        ],
        "answer": "Forbidden"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rechterkant",
        "options": [
            "Honking",
            "Right side",
            "Blue parking disc",
            "The road is wet"
        ],
        "answer": "Right side"
    },
    {
        "question": "Linkerkant",
        "options": [
            "Left side",
            "Honking",
            "Road surface",
            "High beam"
        ],
        "answer": "Left side"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kruispunt",
        "options": [
            "Responsible",
            "Road works",
            "Intersection",
            "Distance"
        ],
        "answer": "Intersection"
    },
    {
        "question": "Reflector",
        "options": [
            "Police and ambulance lights",
            "Reflector",
            "Air conditioner",
            "Disabled vehicle"
        ],
        "answer": "Reflector"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vrachtauto",
        "options": [
            "Broken",
            "Front fog light",
            "Protrudes",
            "Truck"
        ],
        "answer": "Truck"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vrachtwagens",
        "options": [
            "Freight vehicles",
            "Getting out of the car",
            "Left side",
            "Flashing car light"
        ],
        "answer": "Freight vehicles"
    },
    {
        "question": "Landbouwtrekkers",
        "options": [
            "Luggage box",
            "Construction tractors",
            "Pay attention to",
            "Warning lights"
        ],
        "answer": "Construction tractors"
    },
    {
        "question": "Niets",
        "options": [
            "Electronic boards",
            "Flashing yellow light",
            "Nothing",
            "Flashing warning lights"
        ],
        "answer": "Nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "Alarmlichten",
        "options": [
            "Warning lights",
            "Grant",
            "Turning",
            "Flashing yellow light"
        ],
        "answer": "Warning lights"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gehandicapte voertuig",
        "options": [
            "Revolutions per minute (on the meter)",
            "Broken",
            "Disabled vehicle",
            "Injured"
        ],
        "answer": "Disabled vehicle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ruiter",
        "options": [
            "Revolutions per minute (on the meter)",
            "Rider",
            "Front fog light",
            "Traffic jam"
        ],
        "answer": "Rider"
    },
    {
        "question": "Onverhard weg",
        "options": [
            "Unpaved road",
            "Road surface",
            "Flashing car light",
            "Curve"
        ],
        "answer": "Unpaved road"
    },
    {
        "question": "Voor laten gaan",
        "options": [
            "Right of way",
            "Blue parking disc",
            "Road surface",
            "Revolutions per minute (on the meter)"
        ],
        "answer": "Right of way"
    },
    {
        "question": "De rotonde",
        "options": [
            "Roundabout",
            "City light",
            "Right rear light",
            "Rear fog light"
        ],
        "answer": "Roundabout"
    },
    {
        "question": "Militaire colonne",
        "options": [
            "Truck",
            "Shark teeth",
            "Military convoy",
            "Urban area"
        ],
        "answer": "Military convoy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Haaientanden",
        "options": [
            "Revolutions per minute (on the meter)",
            "Urban area",
            "Tire grooves",
            "Shark teeth"
        ],
        "answer": "Shark teeth"
    },
    {
        "question": "Skater",
        "options": [
            "Skater",
            "Front seat",
            "Exiting the road",
            "Trailer"
        ],
        "answer": "Skater"
    },
    {
        "question": "Claxon",
        "options": [
            "Car horn",
            "Front seat",
            "Freight vehicles",
            "Distance"
        ],
        "answer": "Car horn"
    },
    {
        "question": "Autogordel",
        "options": [
            "Seatbelt",
            "Responsible",
            "Right side",
            "Honking"
        ],
        "answer": "Seatbelt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Verantwoordelijk",
        "options": [
            "Police and ambulance lights",
            "Tread depth or thickness",
            "Military convoy",
            "Responsible"
        ],
        "answer": "Responsible"
    },
    {
        "question": "Handrem",
        "options": [
            "Handbrake",
            "Freight vehicles",
            "Touring bus",
            "Specific speed"
        ],
        "answer": "Handbrake"
    },
    {
        "question": "Snelheidsmeter",
        "options": [
            "Responsible",
            "Speedometer",
            "Honking",
            "Seatbelt"
        ],
        "answer": "Speedometer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hoofdsteun",
        "options": [
            "Headrest",
            "Losing control",
            "Car horn",
            "Driving in reverse"
        ],
        "answer": "Headrest"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kentekenplaat",
        "options": [
            "Revolutions per minute (on the meter)",
            "Flashing yellow light",
            "License plate",
            "Minimum speed"
        ],
        "answer": "License plate"
    },
    {
        "question": "Volgafstand",
        "options": [
            "Air conditioner",
            "Sober",
            "Turning around",
            "Following distance"
        ],
        "answer": "Following distance"
    },
    {
        "question": "Skibox",
        "options": [
            "Handbrake",
            "Accurately",
            "Luggage box",
            "Flashing car light"
        ],
        "answer": "Luggage box"
    },
    {
        "question": "Brandstof",
        "options": [
            "Fuel",
            "Child safety seat",
            "Traffic jam",
            "Traffic sign"
        ],
        "answer": "Fuel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Airco",
        "options": [
            "Specific speed",
            "Broken line",
            "Air conditioner",
            "Entering a road"
        ],
        "answer": "Air conditioner"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kinderbeveiligingsmiddel",
        "options": [
            "Passenger",
            "Child safety seat",
            "Rider",
            "Protrudes"
        ],
        "answer": "Child safety seat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Voorste stoel",
        "options": [
            "Board",
            "Front seat",
            "License plate",
            "Branched"
        ],
        "answer": "Front seat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Achterbank",
        "options": [
            "Back seat",
            "Electronic boards",
            "Right rear light",
            "Passenger"
        ],
        "answer": "Back seat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Oversteken",
        "options": [
            "Highway",
            "Street crossing (for pedestrians)",
            "Tunnel",
            "Fuel"
        ],
        "answer": "Street crossing (for pedestrians)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Touringcar",
        "options": [
            "Turning on the lights",
            "Touring bus",
            "Reduce speed",
            "Tire grooves"
        ],
        "answer": "Touring bus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Laadvermogen",
        "options": [
            "Low beam",
            "Load capacity",
            "Electronic boards",
            "The road is slippery"
        ],
        "answer": "Load capacity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Nuchter",
        "options": [
            "Warning triangle",
            "Military convoy",
            "Sober",
            "Continue driving"
        ],
        "answer": "Sober"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bepalen",
        "options": [
            "Freight vehicles",
            "Losing control",
            "Determine",
            "Part"
        ],
        "answer": "Determine"
    },
    {
        "question": "Locatie",
        "options": [
            "Location",
            "Following distance",
            "Merging onto the road",
            "Skater"
        ],
        "answer": "Location"
    },
    {
        "question": "Nauwkeurig",
        "options": [
            "Prohibition",
            "Side street",
            "Accurately",
            "Roundabout"
        ],
        "answer": "Accurately"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hoofdgroeven van een band",
        "options": [
            "Rear fog light",
            "Tire grooves",
            "Blue parking disc",
            "Sober"
        ],
        "answer": "Tire grooves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Inrijden",
        "options": [
            "Entering a road",
            "Car breakdown",
            "Pedestrians",
            "Side street"
        ],
        "answer": "Entering a road"
    },
    {
        "question": "Achteruit rijden",
        "options": [
            "Determine",
            "Warning triangle",
            "Driving in reverse",
            "Low beam"
        ],
        "answer": "Driving in reverse"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bepaalde snelheid",
        "options": [
            "Pedestrians",
            "Specific speed",
            "Trailer",
            "Honking"
        ],
        "answer": "Specific speed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bocht",
        "options": [
            "Curve",
            "Specific speed",
            "Headrest",
            "Right side"
        ],
        "answer": "Curve"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bord",
        "options": [
            "Railway crossing",
            "Urban area",
            "Speedometer",
            "Board"
        ],
        "answer": "Board"
    },
    {
        "question": "Elektrische borden",
        "options": [
            "Street crossing (for pedestrians)",
            "Minimum speed",
            "Honking",
            "Electronic boards"
        ],
        "answer": "Electronic boards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Verplichte snelheidsborden",
        "options": [
            "Mandatory speed signs",
            "Losing control",
            "Road surface",
            "Motor vehicles"
        ],
        "answer": "Mandatory speed signs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tunnel",
        "options": [
            "Vehicle",
            "Losing control",
            "Affects",
            "Tunnel"
        ],
        "answer": "Tunnel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Berm",
        "options": [
            "Accidents",
            "Road works",
            "Grass",
            "Police and ambulance lights"
        ],
        "answer": "Grass"
    },
    {
        "question": "Invoegen",
        "options": [
            "Flashing car light",
            "Merging onto the road",
            "Curve",
            "Forbidden"
        ],
        "answer": "Merging onto the road"
    },
    {
        "question": "Uitvoegen",
        "options": [
            "Exiting the road",
            "Air conditioner",
            "Broken",
            "Distance"
        ],
        "answer": "Exiting the road"
    },
    {
        "question": "Doorrijden",
        "options": [
            "Sober",
            "Continue driving",
            "The road is slippery",
            "Braking"
        ],
        "answer": "Continue driving"
    },
    {
        "question": "Per ongeluk",
        "options": [
            "Affects",
            "Entire road including emergency lane",
            "Motor vehicles",
            "By mistake"
        ],
        "answer": "By mistake"
    },
    {
        "question": "Toegestaan",
        "options": [
            "Air conditioner",
            "Allowed",
            "Seatbelt",
            "Right side"
        ],
        "answer": "Allowed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Doorgetrokken streep",
        "options": [
            "Allowed",
            "Left side",
            "Solid line",
            "Pay attention to"
        ],
        "answer": "Solid line"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rijbaan",
        "options": [
            "Right rear light",
            "Turning on the lights",
            "Roadway (includes multiple lanes)",
            "Tires"
        ],
        "answer": "Roadway (includes multiple lanes)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vluchtstrook",
        "options": [
            "Emergency lane",
            "Drivers",
            "Priority",
            "Pedestrians"
        ],
        "answer": "Emergency lane"
    },
    {
        "question": "Invoegstrook",
        "options": [
            "Trailer",
            "Child safety seat",
            "Temporary stop",
            "Entry lane"
        ],
        "answer": "Entry lane"
    },
    {
        "question": "Onderbroken streep",
        "options": [
            "Broken line",
            "Front seat",
            "Seatbelt",
            "Roadway (includes multiple lanes)"
        ],
        "answer": "Broken line"
    },
    {
        "question": "Wegdek",
        "options": [
            "Road surface",
            "Fuel",
            "Driving lane",
            "Police and ambulance lights"
        ],
        "answer": "Road surface"
    },
    {
        "question": "Intermitterende lichten",
        "options": [
            "Nothing",
            "Flashing yellow light",
            "Road surface",
            "Air conditioner"
        ],
        "answer": "Flashing yellow light"
    },
    {
        "question": "Verkeerslichten",
        "options": [
            "Warning triangle",
            "Traffic light",
            "Entry lane",
            "Injured"
        ],
        "answer": "Traffic light"
    },
    {
        "question": "Richtingaanwijzer",
        "options": [
            "Turn signal",
            "Street crossing (for pedestrians)",
            "High beam",
            "Warning lights"
        ],
        "answer": "Turn signal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zijweg",
        "options": [
            "By mistake",
            "Skater",
            "Forbidden",
            "Side street"
        ],
        "answer": "Side street"
    },
    {
        "question": "Beide zijden",
        "options": [
            "Both sides",
            "Continue driving",
            "Mandatory speed signs",
            "Releasing the gas pedal"
        ],
        "answer": "Both sides"
    },
    {
        "question": "Afslaag",
        "options": [
            "Branched",
            "Flashing yellow light",
            "Accurately",
            "Road works"
        ],
        "answer": "Branched"
    },
    {
        "question": "Afslaan",
        "options": [
            "Turning",
            "Affects",
            "Roundabout",
            "Sober"
        ],
        "answer": "Turning"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gedeelte",
        "options": [
            "Part",
            "Turn signal",
            "One-way road",
            "Right side"
        ],
        "answer": "Part"
    },
    {
        "question": "Snelweg",
        "options": [
            "Exiting the road",
            "Highway",
            "Pedestrians",
            "Grant"
        ],
        "answer": "Highway"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rijstrook",
        "options": [
            "Loading goods",
            "Driving lane",
            "Reduce speed",
            "Car horn"
        ],
        "answer": "Driving lane"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rechterrijstrook",
        "options": [
            "Right driving lane",
            "Tunnel",
            "Priority",
            "Injured"
        ],
        "answer": "Right driving lane"
    },
    {
        "question": "Uitvoegstrook",
        "options": [
            "Exit lane",
            "Flashing car light",
            "Merging onto the road",
            "High beam"
        ],
        "answer": "Exit lane"
    },
    {
        "question": "Weg",
        "options": [
            "Roadway (includes multiple lanes)",
            "Rear fog light",
            "Entire road including emergency lane",
            "Determine"
        ],
        "answer": "Entire road including emergency lane"
    },
    {
        "question": "Schuld",
        "options": [
            "Trailer",
            "Turning around",
            "Fine",
            "Branched"
        ],
        "answer": "Fine"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dimlicht",
        "options": [
            "Flashing warning lights",
            "Location",
            "Low beam",
            "Electronic boards"
        ],
        "answer": "Low beam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stadslicht",
        "options": [
            "Air conditioner",
            "Side street",
            "City light",
            "Load capacity"
        ],
        "answer": "City light"
    },
    {
        "question": "Grootlicht",
        "options": [
            "Accurately",
            "High beam",
            "Public transport",
            "Highway"
        ],
        "answer": "High beam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mistachterlicht",
        "options": [
            "Rear fog light",
            "Allowed",
            "Revolutions per minute (on the meter)",
            "Front fog light"
        ],
        "answer": "Rear fog light"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mistvoorlicht",
        "options": [
            "Front fog light",
            "Entering a road",
            "Tires",
            "Grant"
        ],
        "answer": "Front fog light"
    },
    {
        "question": "Linkerachterlicht",
        "options": [
            "Losing control",
            "Entry lane",
            "Left rear light",
            "Tread depth or thickness"
        ],
        "answer": "Left rear light"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rechterachterlicht",
        "options": [
            "License plate",
            "Grass",
            "Right rear light",
            "Rider"
        ],
        "answer": "Right rear light"
    },
    {
        "question": "Parkeerschijf",
        "options": [
            "Flashing yellow light",
            "Blue parking disc",
            "Passenger",
            "Prohibition"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue parking disc"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stuk",
        "options": [
            "Car breakdown",
            "Parking",
            "Priority",
            "Broken"
        ],
        "answer": "Broken"
    },
    {
        "question": "Passagier",
        "options": [
            "Passenger",
            "Load capacity",
            "Continue driving",
            "Freight vehicles"
        ],
        "answer": "Passenger"
    },
    {
        "question": "Uitstappen van de auto",
        "options": [
            "Getting out of the car",
            "Luggage box",
            "Road surface",
            "Revolutions per minute (on the meter)"
        ],
        "answer": "Getting out of the car"
    },
    {
        "question": "Goederen laden",
        "options": [
            "Residential area",
            "Nothing",
            "Loading goods",
            "Road works"
        ],
        "answer": "Loading goods"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lichten branden",
        "options": [
            "Getting out of the car",
            "Broken line",
            "Turning on the lights",
            "Back seat"
        ],
        "answer": "Turning on the lights"
    },
    {
        "question": "Knipperende waarschuwingslichten",
        "options": [
            "Part",
            "Merging onto the road",
            "Aquaplaning",
            "Flashing warning lights"
        ],
        "answer": "Flashing warning lights"
    },
    {
        "question": "De weg is glad",
        "options": [
            "Solid line",
            "Car horn",
            "The road is slippery",
            "Curve"
        ],
        "answer": "The road is slippery"
    },
    {
        "question": "De weg is nat",
        "options": [
            "Merging onto the road",
            "Speedometer",
            "The road is wet",
            "Tunnel"
        ],
        "answer": "The road is wet"
    },
    {
        "question": "Werkzaamheden",
        "options": [
            "Determine",
            "Sober",
            "Road works",
            "Headrest"
        ],
        "answer": "Road works"
    },
    {
        "question": "Weersomstandigheden",
        "options": [
            "Tires",
            "Grass",
            "Exit lane",
            "Weather conditions"
        ],
        "answer": "Weather conditions"
    },
    {
        "question": "Controle verliezen",
        "options": [
            "Fine",
            "Skater",
            "Losing control",
            "Specific speed"
        ],
        "answer": "Losing control"
    },
    {
        "question": "Afstand",
        "options": [
            "Blue parking disc",
            "Distance",
            "Seatbelt",
            "Arrow"
        ],
        "answer": "Distance"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gevarendriehoek",
        "options": [
            "Distance",
            "Right rear light",
            "Warning triangle",
            "Emergency lane"
        ],
        "answer": "Warning triangle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zwaaiende sirenes",
        "options": [
            "Road surface",
            "Arrow",
            "Freight vehicles",
            "Police and ambulance lights"
        ],
        "answer": "Police and ambulance lights"
    },
    {
        "question": "Toeteren",
        "options": [
            "Responds",
            "Electronic boards",
            "Honking",
            "Tunnel"
        ],
        "answer": "Honking"
    },
    {
        "question": "Knipperen",
        "options": [
            "Braking",
            "Flashing car light",
            "Grass",
            "Drivers"
        ],
        "answer": "Flashing car light"
    },
    {
        "question": "File op de weg",
        "options": [
            "Location",
            "Protrudes",
            "Traffic jam",
            "Intersection"
        ],
        "answer": "Traffic jam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Langzamer rijden",
        "options": [
            "Parking",
            "Turning",
            "Reduce speed",
            "Construction tractors"
        ],
        "answer": "Reduce speed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Remmen",
        "options": [
            "Luggage box",
            "Braking",
            "Rear fog light",
            "Warning triangle"
        ],
        "answer": "Braking"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gas los laten",
        "options": [
            "Traffic jam",
            "By mistake",
            "Parking",
            "Releasing the gas pedal"
        ],
        "answer": "Releasing the gas pedal"
    }
]